CONTACT



ALBIN JOSE

- @ albinjosemtd@gmail.com
- **** +91-9995833835
- Kizhakkepallivathukal(H), mukkulam east p.o mukkulam, Idukki-686514

ABOUT

Experienced Technical Support Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the electrical and electronic manufacturing industry. Skilled in AutoCAD, ERP software, electrical estimating, power systems, electrical panel design, and electrical engineering. Professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B. Tech), focused in Electrical and Electronics Engineering from Mahatma Gandhi University.

EXPERIENCE

07/05/2018 - 01/03/2019

KSCSTE (Kerala State Council for Science Technology and Environment)

Independent Research Scientist
On Internal Combustion Engines

14/06/2019 -15/09/2019

OEN India Limited

Apprentice

I have worked in the production line of 74 series relay. Stacking, welding, testing, reporting and on time filling of records are my duties.

11/11/2019 -15/09/2020

IYYM Engineering Services Pvt Ltd

Technical Support Engineer

Estimation of Electrical control panels such as star-delta, DOL, soft starter, VFD starter distribution panels and electrical scope for instrumentation (flow, level, pressure, temperature instruments and integration).

Preparation if Technical documents referring to client requirements and specification.

Preparation of Electrical drawing in AutoCAD incorporating the customer specific logic operation.

EDUCATION

2011-2013

JJ Murphy Memirial Higher Secondary School, Yendayar

Biology Science

72%

2013-2017

MG University

Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Second Class

SKILLS	
	AutoCAD Electrical
	Competente with most MS Office programs
	ERP
	Good understanding of Electrical Drawings
LANGUAGE	
	English
	Malayalam

Tamil

Hindi